[{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980384864,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":21050,"timeElapsed":147792},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980400641,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":15776,"timeElapsed":163569},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980412371,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":11728,"timeElapsed":175299},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980424698,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":12328,"timeElapsed":187626},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980436708,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":12009,"timeElapsed":199636},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980446438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":9728,"timeElapsed":209366},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980452929,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":6490,"timeElapsed":215857},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980460199,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":7268,"timeElapsed":223126},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980467010,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"151","question":"What was or is your favorite class in school? Why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":6809,"timeElapsed":229938},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980484553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":15310,"timeElapsed":247481},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980488840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":4286,"timeElapsed":251768},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980493993,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":5151,"timeElapsed":256920},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980498627,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":4634,"timeElapsed":261555},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980504963,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":6335,"timeElapsed":267891},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980509634,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":4670,"timeElapsed":272562},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980515403,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":5768,"timeElapsed":278331},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980520031,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":4627,"timeElapsed":282959},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980523654,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"209","question":"Do you cook often? What is your favorite meal or dish to cook and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3621,"timeElapsed":286582},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980536328,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":87,"rt":10837,"timeElapsed":299256},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980539933,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":81,"rt":3604,"timeElapsed":302861},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980545113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":5181,"timeElapsed":308041},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980548670,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":3556,"timeElapsed":311598},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980552736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4065,"timeElapsed":315664},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980557747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5010,"timeElapsed":320675},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980561438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3690,"timeElapsed":324366},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980565854,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":4415,"timeElapsed":328782},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980569315,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"21","question":"What roles do love and affection play in your life?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3460,"timeElapsed":332243},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980578298,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7022,"timeElapsed":341226},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980583253,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":4955,"timeElapsed":346181},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980586684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3430,"timeElapsed":349612},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980590145,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":3460,"timeElapsed":353073},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980593828,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":90,"rt":3681,"timeElapsed":356756},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980596809,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":2981,"timeElapsed":359737},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980601338,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":4529,"timeElapsed":364266},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980604827,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":367755},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980608374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"20","question":"What does friendship mean to you?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3545,"timeElapsed":371302},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980620585,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":10073,"timeElapsed":383513},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980625859,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5272,"timeElapsed":388786},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980628944,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":74,"rt":3085,"timeElapsed":391872},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980631880,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":2935,"timeElapsed":394808},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980634684,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":2803,"timeElapsed":397612},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980637235,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":2550,"timeElapsed":400163},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980641939,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4702,"timeElapsed":404867},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980645048,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":3108,"timeElapsed":407976},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980647820,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"48","question":"Do you believe in fate or destiny? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2771,"timeElapsed":410748},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980656613,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":7147,"timeElapsed":419541},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980661123,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4511,"timeElapsed":424051},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980664496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3372,"timeElapsed":427424},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980668522,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":4025,"timeElapsed":431450},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980672035,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":3512,"timeElapsed":434963},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980685713,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":13677,"timeElapsed":448641},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980689977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":4263,"timeElapsed":452905},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980695169,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":5191,"timeElapsed":458097},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980698766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3596,"timeElapsed":461694},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980702322,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"160","question":"What foreign country would you most like to visit? What attracts you to this place?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":3554,"timeElapsed":465250},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980712721,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8737,"timeElapsed":475649},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980716015,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":3293,"timeElapsed":478943},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980719138,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3122,"timeElapsed":482066},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980722460,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3322,"timeElapsed":485388},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980728794,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6333,"timeElapsed":491722},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980731919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3123,"timeElapsed":494847},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980736186,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4266,"timeElapsed":499114},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980739813,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3626,"timeElapsed":502741},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980743543,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"129","question":"When you think about the future, what do you most think about?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3730,"timeElapsed":506471},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980754970,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":9900,"timeElapsed":517898},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980757921,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":2950,"timeElapsed":520849},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980760841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2920,"timeElapsed":523769},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980763442,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2600,"timeElapsed":526370},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980766334,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":2891,"timeElapsed":529262},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980768860,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2524,"timeElapsed":531788},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980772788,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3927,"timeElapsed":535716},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980775822,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3033,"timeElapsed":538750},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980778452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"103","question":"What’s one thing about yourself you hope will never change?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":2629,"timeElapsed":541379},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980788865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":8859,"timeElapsed":551793},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980794142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5276,"timeElapsed":557070},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980797374,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3231,"timeElapsed":560302},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980800393,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":3018,"timeElapsed":563321},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980803676,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":3282,"timeElapsed":566604},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980817804,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":14127,"timeElapsed":580732},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980821656,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3851,"timeElapsed":584584},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980827555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":33,"rt":5899,"timeElapsed":590483},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980831227,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3670,"timeElapsed":594155},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980834906,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"153","question":"What was the most recent gift you gave somebody? What was the reason or context?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":88,"rt":3679,"timeElapsed":597834},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980844919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":8102,"timeElapsed":607847},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980848466,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3546,"timeElapsed":611394},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980851719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":3252,"timeElapsed":614647},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980855249,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3528,"timeElapsed":618176},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980858902,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":3653,"timeElapsed":621830},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980861991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":3088,"timeElapsed":624919},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980866683,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4691,"timeElapsed":629611},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980870161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":3477,"timeElapsed":633089},{"subjectID":"kox9ghrcq8","prolificID":"60c0b72e6692e0a14776eafd","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"6769b267cebb15471e2eef37","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1734980873962,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"237","question":"How is your day going?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":3800,"timeElapsed":636890}]